What a lively crowd.
The Farsas king's birthday is now an annual
event where we welcome foreign diplomats.
Apologies in advance for all the trouble.
I knew what I was getting into.
Oh, that's right.
Let me see your hand.
This is a magic implement.
It can be used once by sliding the stone,
which will prevent any teleportation
magic in your immediate surroundings.
After the hard time we had in that fight, huh?
Teleportation and flight can be a real hassle.
Will it stop you from teleporting, too?
It will.
I created it to stop even those with
powers comparable to a witch's.
Happy birthday.
What's wrong?
Is something funny?
No, of course that's your gift.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
~ Half of Eternity ~
Pleased to make your
acquaintances, Your Majesties.
My name is Aurelia Canao Naysha Faurecia.
I come here from Gandona in place
of our king to offer his congratulations.
Thank you for the courteous introduction.
Please send the king my regards.
Why, of course.
Hey, you two.
Travis.
How dare you...
Hey, show some prudence.
I'm here as her guardian.
I'd like you to serve
as a stand-in for my girl.
A stand-in?
A pesky woman might show up
to try and kill Aurelia.
We don't want her underlings to come
here while I make my way to go kill her.
So for the time being,
you'll be my girl instead.
What?
Don't I get a say in this?
By the way, what's this pesky woman like?
She's just like me.
You mean she's got a nasty personality?
Not that.
I mean in terms of rank.
She's a demon queen?!
Anyway, you don't get to say no here.
Wait, wait, wait!
If you cooperate, I promise
that both Farsas and Tuldarr,
as long as your bloodline lives on,
will be free of my aggression.
Be it one country or two,
it's all the same to me.
What is your relationship with Aurelia?
Huh? Nothing, really.
I've just taken a liking to her.
She's still a child, so it'd be
a shame if she died.
So will you do it or not?
F-Fine, I will.
Blossom.
This sign proves you're mine.
Any demon would recognize it.
Ugh...
I'll check her dressing room.
Please do.
Seriously, when did she manage to sneak out?
Queen Tinasha?
No way!
It's not someone's missing child, is it?
What do I do?
I'll take that.
Thanks a lot.
There, there.
Th-The letter! The letter!
Could this be...
Y-You've got it all wrong!
Tinasha. I was looking for you.
"This infant is the king's child."
"Please raise him well."
Huh?
That's not my child.
Th-That's right!
His Majesty would never be so foolish!
Do the two of you think I'm stupid?
There's no way the math would work out.
Oh, right.
It's been two months since
Queen Tinasha lifted the curse.
There hasn't been enough time...
Um, so in that case...
An abandoned child?
Do you know who could have done this?
No.
I don't recognize the handwriting.
And there's no name given here.
Well, we can keep an eye
on him in Farsas for now.
The mother might change her mind
and come back for him.
That's true.
I-I'm sorry.
I have an errand to run, so I'll be leaving.
That sure is sudden.
Are you angry?
Eh?
At Lazar's mindless comments just now?
Ah...
Yep, I'm mad.
Which is why I'm leaving.
Hey...
Wait up.
No, thanks.
See you later.
Something's bugging me...
Lanak?
A dream?
What's wrong?
I had a dream.
A dream where I got stabbed.
You saw into her memories?
I'll get rid of them.
They're not good for you.
Aurelia.
What is it?
I'll be away from the mansion for a bit.
If any strangers come by asking for me,
tell them I've taken a liking to that woman.
By "that woman," you
mean the queen of Tuldarr?
Yes.
Don't you dare leave this mansion.
S-Sure.
So?
What kind of woman is the puppet this time?
She's a powerful mage, for a human.
However...
Phaedra    Higher Demon
Twelve of our kind serve her.
Nothing more than scum, serving a lowly insect.
What disgraces.
Should we end their lives while we're at it?
Before you can do that...
I'll end yours first.
Travis!
You came all this way for me?
It's about time you stop
following me around, Phaedra.
I'm done giving you the time of day.
I've sealed off your escape.
Come out, Phaedra.
What's the big idea, Taviti?
Where did Phaedra go?
She's descended to the human realm.
You're up against me.
Which means...
Well, she can handle it herself.
Phaedra is...
Wicked.
Haughty.
Sadistic.
She's been obsessed with Lord Travis for ages.
I hear she's manifested herself in the human
realm just to kill humans close to him.
She's just like Lady Tinasha.
Way too attached.
I'd never kill my romantic rivals!
Looks like she's here.
So you're the pesky insect.
You should be honored to die by my hand.
Travis, you idiot!
Is this... the old capital?
Yes.
Found you.
So sneaky and annoying.
Itz, Senn, Saiha, Lilia, Kunai, Eir, Sylpha!
Work together to prevent
any magic from escaping the area.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'm ready to kill you.
Come at me as you wish.
What nonsense!
Travis disappeared?
Yes.
He said he'd be back soon,
but he still hasn't returned.
I thought Queen Tinasha
might know where he went,
but she was nowhere
to be found in Tuldarr, either.
Tinasha's gone missing as well?!
They say she was in her office until noon.
There were burn marks in her office,
which could be a sign of magic.
She got involved with that man?
Sorry, I'm going to go pay Tuldarr a visit.
I'll inspect the fortress at a later date.
Yes!
I-I'll go with you!
I'm a mage, too.
Please take me with you.
Still...
As a mage, you'll be defending yourself.
Y-Yes!
Is something the matter?
Why is he here?
Oscar!
Oh? What's the matter?
Nothing.
Just felt a little sleepy.
Something happened to
the defensive barrier I put on Oscar.
Then slumber eternally!
But right now...
How unpleasant.
Before he has his way
with that tender body of yours,
I'll butcher you until not
a single drop of blood remains!
I'll have faith in Oscar!
It's been chasing after me?
Your Majesty, you must not make contact!
Let us teleport for now.
I'll look into that child's past.
I may be able to find a way
to dispel that miasma.
I'll buy you time.
I gaze upon days gone by.
Your Majesty.
Do you know the name Simila?
Yeah.
It's the forbidden curse that Cezar summoned.
I think its core was negative human emotions,
and it draws its power from another realm.
That baby was sent to assassinate Your Majesty,
with unshapen remnants
of Simila sealed within him.
Evil that lacks composition...
Negative emotions...
That must be why it wasn't detected by magic.
There's a mark on his body
to bind the remnants to him.
If you destroy it...
We can sever the connection?
Your Majesty!
She hasn't rushed here yet.
Which means she's in no position to move.
I need to hurry.
You sure did turn out to be a hassle.
I must say, how fragile.
There's only one person
who holds the privilege of killing me.
How did you...
This is the end for you.
It's all the same...
Resentment...
Resignation, anguish...
All the same...
All connected...
I see.
Negative human emotions.
The sorrow will never subside...
Become one...
Spare me that rubbish.
I'm different from all of you!
That's a good boy.
Bear with it, just a little.
Please show me your wounds!
You should tend to him first.
Oscar!
Tinasha!
What happened to you?
Eh?
N-Nothing.
Don't tell such obvious lies!
Where's that man?
Travis hasn't come back yet?
Don't tell me he lost...
You know I'd never lose.
Be a little more serious.
Travis!
Where have you been?!
I've been worried sick!
I'm just fine, so no need to worry.
If you're fine, I wish you
would have helped out here.
Here?
Well, it's a long story...
You can tell me all about it later.
So, does that wrap up this case, then?
Yeah.
I'll keep my promise.
That said, looks like you took a real beating.
That's amazing.
A bonus for making you take on Phaedra.
Okay, let's go home, Aurelia.
You deceived me?
It was that little brat, not this girl?
Tinasha.
Don't tell me...
An aftershock?
Get out!
There's no place here for you!
That's not good.
What's going on?
Did someone possess her?
Phaedra is nothing more than remnants now.
She can't possibly possess anyone.
But the demon realm is out of equilibrium
after suddenly losing its queen.
We're seeing the aftershocks
as it tries to return to normal.
Aftershocks?
It's trying to have her
replace the queen she killed
by infusing her with tremendous power.
But no matter how high your magic tolerance
is, you'll go berserk if you're subjected to that.
Huh?
Damn it.
Tinasha!
Can't we stop it somehow?!
Once she's like that, there's no way.
Are you insane?
Akashia may have the advantage,
but blind faith in it will get you killed.
I can't let her run loose.
She's my woman.
We need to talk, Tinasha.
No. Go away!
If you hate me so much, come down here.
I'll take you on in a fight.
Then perish!
Get down here already!
I hate you.
Come back to your senses, Tinasha!
Shut up!
Just disappear!
I-I hate you!
I hate you, I hate you!
I hate you, I hate you, I hate you!
I hate you!
Get out of my sight!
There should be no reason for me to be sad.
Die!
Just die, you big liar!
I hate you, I hate you, I hate you!
Why do you hate me?
Because I'm mortal?
I hate you.
You're nothing but a liar.
I hate you so much!
I want you so much...
I can't stand it!
You won't ever be mine.
You're going to leave me.
I won't leave you.
I'm yours to take.
I hate you.
What I want is...
Love me...
Have you been worried about that all this time?
I really do love you.
Don't worry.
I swear.
Don't undo the seal without my permission.
Sneaking out of the mansion as well.
You little rascal.
Then let me say this.
If you want to continue
to spend your life with me,
stop it with those wicked acts of yours!
Do that, and I'll bear half of
your outrageous sins.
Are you an idiot?
You'll only end up unhappy.
First off, why did you volunteer
yourself for such a painful task?
That's because...
I'm indebted to him.
He's the one who suggested
I put myself in that magic slumber.
Truth be told, I hadn't
even considered the idea
of coming here to meet you.
We come from different eras,
and there was no guarantee.
Until Travis told me,
"Stop moping and go find him."
That said, we're even now.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
I see.
I'll be back soon to see you again.
I really do love you so much.
I was lying when I said, "I hate you."
I know.
The seeds are sown in silence.
Hazily, as though in a dream,
they all subtly begin to take root.
And when they see the radiant flowers blooming,
that is when they
will finally realize, all too late...
That the final upheaval has already begun.
~ Pride of the Past ~